<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Hong Jeon</title>
 <link href="http://hongjeon.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://hongjeon.com/"/>
 <updated>2016-03-24T03:03:15-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://hongjeon.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Mark Otto</name>
   <email>markdotto@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>What's a blog?</title>
   <link href="http://hongjeon.com/whats-blog"/>
   <updated>2016-03-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hongjeon.com/whats-blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I think we’ll always look back at our writing and think it was bad, because it’s a pretty much a reflection of our thoughts, which get more complex with experience” - Jeffrey Terry&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time, it seems that brilliant realizations come to me only at 3:00AM. As I sit in my college apartment, regretting the time I’ve spent putting together this website, the clock reads 3:17, and I’m starting to question if all ideas naturally seem like great ideas at this hour..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making a blog was definitely not in my agenda even 5 hours ago, but earlier today, Arpita Ghosh and her Networks homework was easily pushed aside in favor of watching videos on Facebook. Specifically, I saw a weight-loss transformation of a guy who literally ended up losing 200 pounds and turning his life around. At the end, he looked back on what was probably the hardest journey in his entire life and, very understandably, he was emotional about it. Normally, I would be back to scrolling for the next video, but un-understandably(?), I, who is least likely to understand what he went through, felt something click in my head. Somewhere, for some reason, I had the sudden compelling urgency and motivation to break out of habit and actually do &lt;em&gt;something,&lt;/em&gt; because god dammit I wanted to change my life too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This reaction seemed odd since things had been going well recently, but for some time now, I couldn’t shake the feeling that Life is a circus and I’m just jumping through hoops. I was always moving quickly, but the thing with these routines is that you never quite know where you’re going until you see the next hoop. According to &lt;cite&gt;Inside Out&lt;/cite&gt;, Life is made up of the accumilations of thousands of tiny decisions that you make everyday. If I’m absorbed in a routine without thinking, then am I really making choices for myself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As graduation approaches, I am prompted to think more frequently about the career path that I have to make, and all the hoops I’ve jumped through. The big decisions I’ve had to make until now seemed pale in comparison to picking a career that I’ll be pursing until I &lt;strong&gt;die&lt;/strong&gt;. If I had to pick a time to stop jumping through hoops, it might as well be now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this blog is my little spark of defiance against regularity, old-habits, and hoops. If I know I’m rubbish at writing, then putting up a website with only writing will surely be the most uncomfortable thing for me at this critical junction in life. If this means that I have to continue to write meaningless blog posts to kindle some sort of rebellion, then I will continue doing so, and maybe somewhere down the line, they will eventually become meaningful to me.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
